

JEFFRY HERMANTO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Experienced mobile app & website developer who has a track record of success creating apps & websites that are both well-received & commercially viable. Skilled with working as a team & incorporating input into projects. Ability to always look for ways to improve upon an already existing app to keep people downloading it & enjoying it. Strong eye for detail & tenacity to never quit on something until it is absolutely perfect.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Birth date

October 23rd, 1978

Nationality

Indonesian

Address

Arcadia Village Jl. Rolin No. 11 Gading Serpong Tangerang Selatan - 15810

CONTACT

- jeffryhermanto@gmail.com
- +62 821 7777 1078
- www.jeffryhermanto.com
- /jeffryhermanto

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

• Manager - Divisi Application Development, Architecture & Governance

PT BANK RAYA INDONESIA

2021 - Present

Build & ship digital banking applications. Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features. Work on bug fixing and improving application performance. Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency. Write clean and readable code. Make use of App Architecture, Design patterns, and advanced Git in order to produce highly maintainable code.

Web and Application Developer

PT TRADECORP INDONESIA

Aug 2020 - Present

Create SEO friendly websites conforming SEO best practices and develop mobile applications from ideation until completion.

Senior Mobile Engineer

OFLOAD (PREVIOUSLY LOADSMILE) - DIGITAL SERVICES AUSTRALIA IV PTY LTD Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

Build advanced applications for the Android and iOS platforms using Flutter; Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features; Write a clean and readable code as an advanced Git user in order to produce highly maintainable code.

Senior Software Engineer

SPROUT - PT TUNAS DIGITAL INDONESIA

Mar 2019 - Feb 2020

Create, maintain, and implement the source code to develop web / mobile apps/programs that meet the needs and requirements of the clients using Agile principles with the Scrum framework.

iOS Developer

APPLE DEVELOPER ACADEMY

Jun 2018 - Oct 2018

Solving challenges from communities using collaborative approach.

Web & Mobile Developer

FREELANCE 2008 - Present

Designing, implementing, and modifying websites/mobile apps, from layout to function and according to a client's specifications. Strive to create visually appealing sites that feature user-friendly design and clear navigation.

EDUCATION

Fullstack Web & Mobile Developer Certificate

PURWADHIKA STARTUP AND CODING SCHOOL

Jan 2018 - May 2018

Information Technology Related

SELF-TAUGHT 2007 - Present

MAIN SKILLS

Flutter (iOS & Android Development) SvelteKit (Web Development)

BASIC SKILLS

HTML & CSS Javascript Typescript Dart Swift Java Kotlin Node.js OOP

INTEREST

Music Baseball Softball Digital Marketing